http://www.christiancourier.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting this web site. We understand the importance that Internet users place on privacy. This Privacy Policy describes how we use personal information that is collected at this website.
Please read this Privacy Policy before using this site or submitting any personal information. By using this web site, you accept the privacy practices contained in this Privacy Policy. These privacy practices may change from time to time, but any changes will be posted. You are encouraged to review the Privacy Policy whenever you visit the web site to make sure you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Information We Collect
In order to serve our readers and customers, we collect personally identifiable information, such as: names, addresses, phone numbers, email addresses, and sometimes credit card information when such information is voluntarily submitted by our visitors. We will only use your personal information for the following purposes: (1) to deliver the products or services to you that you have requested; (2) to validate your compliance with the terms and conditions; (3) for content improvement and feedback purposes; and (4) to reach you, when necessary, regarding your use of the website or product(s).
Questions or comments submitted through this web site, by email, telephone, postal mail, or any other means become the sole and exclusive property of this website and may be published, retained, or released at our sole discretion. Additionally, this web site reserves the right to edit published questions and comments for spelling, grammar, or general readability.
We will NEVER share your personal contact information with third parties unless you have given us explicit permission to do so, such as in order to fulfill a third party offer that you have accepted from us. By permitting us to collect this information, you agree to receive information on products and services that may be of interest to you, including related third-party offers that we may send to you. You also enable us to personalize your experience on this website or any other publishing medium we produce so that we can provide you with the highest quality of service. By submitting your email address on this website, you agree to receive email communications from us. You can cancel your participation in any of these email lists at any time by clicking the opt-out link or other unsubscribe options that may be included in the respective email. We only send emails to people who have authorized us to contact them, either directly, or through a third party. We do not send unsolicited commercial emails, because we hate spam as much as you do.
In addition, you agree that by submitting your email address on this web site and/or registering to receive a product and/or service offered herein, such act constitutes a purchase, an inquiry, and/or an application for the purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (ATSR), 16 CFR
